<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Family Team</string>
    <string name="about_app">About</string>
    <string name="rules_app">Rules</string>
    <string name="reg_adm" >Reg. new Team</string>
    <string name="by_email">by Email</string>
    <string name="by_phone">by Phone</string>
    <string name="e_mail">Email</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone, only digits with country code</string>
    <string name="email_or_phone">Email/Phone, only digits with country code</string>
    <string name="nick_name">Nick, only letters, numbers and \'_\'</string>
    <string name="display_name">(optional) Display name</string>
    <string name="optional">optional:</string>
    <string name="password">Password, minimum 6 characters</string>
    <string name="reg_button">Register</string>
    <string name="try_again_button">Try again</string>
    <string name="enter_code_from_sms">Enter 6-digit code from SMS</string>
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="button_resend_sms">Resend SMS code</string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="please_verify_email">Please verify your email</string>
    <string name="please_verify_phone">Please verify your phone number</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="coins">Coins</string>
    <string name="tasks">Tasks</string>
    <string name="reminders">Reminders</string>
    <string name="sell"> Sell </string>
    <string name="buy"> Buy </string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete account %s</string>
    <string name="delete_team">Delete ALL TEAM %s</string>
    <string name="enter_password_for_confirm_delete">Enter your password for confirm delete</string>
    <string name="wrong_password">Wrong password</string>

    <string name="rules_text">
        \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0General Information\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0You can
        register your Team as an administrator and create an unlimited number of team members,
        or obtain a Nickname and password from the Administrator and log in to the application
        as a user (the administrator also has all user capabilities). A user can:\n1)
        Create new tasks for themselves, specifying the task time (with push reminders or without,
        up to 3 for each task).\n2) Create new tasks for other Team members (also with up to 3
        reminders).\n3) Maintain a list of planned purchases.\nAdministrators and the first 2 users
        they register without a premium status can create up to %d new tasks daily and use up
        to %d reminders. For other users, the available tasks and reminders do not automatically
        renew daily (they need to purchase Coins or have a Premium status). Maintaining a shopping
        list is unlimited in quantity and does not require Coins.\nIf necessary, any user can buy
        Coins (Team Coins or TC) and exchange them for additional Tasks and Reminders.\nCoins can
        also be used to purchase Premium Status, either for a limited period or indefinitely. In
        this case, the user can create up to %d new tasks and %d new reminders
        daily.\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0Registering a New Team\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0To
        register a new team, click the button \"Reg. new Team\" button.\nThen choose to register
        via email or phone and fill out all the required information. After that, confirm your email
        (a message will be sent to your email address) or phone (a code will be sent via SMS).
        Once confirmed, you will be registered with administrator rights, enabling you to create
        or delete new users. After creating a new user, provide them with their Nickname and
        password, as well as your credentials (email or phone number) for logging into your
        account.\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0Logging into Your Account\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0To
        log in, click the button \"Login\", then enter the administrator’s email or phone number (with
        country code but without the \"+\" sign) in the top field. Next, enter your Nickname and
        password, and click the button \"Login\".
    </string>

    <string name="about_text">
        App name:\n\"Family Team\"\n\nApp author:\nAliaksandr Babrouski\n\nApp
        version: %s\n\ne-mail: balexvicx@gmail.com\n\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0The app is intended for use
        in a family or other groups of people connected in daily life and having common affairs (for
        example, joint rent of housing or working in the same team).\n\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0The app
        allows users to create or delete online tasks for execution (for themselves or other
        group members), as well as a shopping list.
    </string>
</resources>